[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What are bits?",
    "answer": "Any kind of two-valued things, usually described as zeros and ones.",
    "chapter": "chapter1",
    "category": "javascript1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What are values?",
    "answer": "Chunks of bits.",
    "chapter": "chapter1",
    "category": "javascript1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "How many bits are used to store a number?",
    "answer": "64",
    "chapter": "chapter1",
    "category": "javascript1"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What does the Unicode standard do?",
    "answer": "It assigns a number to every character.",
    "chapter": "chapter1",
    "category": "javascript1"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What do you call operators that takes only one operator?",
    "answer": "Unary.",
    "chapter": "chapter1",
    "category": "javascript1"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What do you call operators that takes two operators?",
    "answer": "Binary.",
    "chapter": "chapter1",
    "category": "javascript1"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What do you call operators that takes three operators?",
    "answer": "Ternary (or conditional). For example console.log(false ? 1 : 2); // => 2",
    "chapter": "chapter1",
    "category": "javascript1"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "How does JS compare strings?",
    "answer": "JavaScript goes over the characters from left to right, comparing the Unicode codes one by one.",
    "chapter": "chapter1",
    "category": "javascript1"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Are 'null' and 'undefined' values?",
    "answer": "Yes, but they carry no information.",
    "chapter": "chapter1",
    "category": "javascript1"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is 'type coercion'?",
    "answer": "When an operator is applied to the “wrong” type of value, JavaScript will quietly convert that value to the type it needs.",
    "chapter": "chapter1",
    "category": "javascript1"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "How can you test if a value has a real value instead of 'null' or 'undefned'?",
    "answer": "You can compare the value to null with the == (or !=) operator",
    "chapter": "chapter1",
    "category": "javascript1"
  }
]
